- Did not.
- Did too.
Okay, maybe some of it. But...
(Leonard:)The guy was just in the right place
at the right time...
(Leonard:)...with the right paradigm-shifting
reinterpretation of the universe.
(Leonard:)He got lucky.
(Raj:)In more ways than one.
(Raj:)He's a very handsome man.
(Howard:)Doesn't do anything for me.
If I was gonna go that way...
...I'm more of a Zac Efron kind of guy.
(Raj:)Oh, yeah.
Like you have a shot with Zac Efron.
(David(approaching):)Excuse me. Are you Leonard Hofstadter?
- Uh, yeah.
- I'm David Underhill.
Uh, yeah. Heh, heh.
(David:)Dr. Gablehauser said
if I wanted to set up something in the lab...
(David:)...that you'd be able to give me a hand?
- You wanna work with me?
- If you have time, yeah.
Wow. Yeah, sure. Yeah, no problem.
Um, here's my home number,
here's my cell, here's my office...
(Leonard:)...here's my parents' number
up in New Jersey.
- They know how to reach me.
DAVID: Okay.
(Leonard:)Congratulations on the MacArthur grant,
by the way. Big fan.
(David:)Thanks. I'll call you.
(Howard:)Okay.
(Leonard:)Bye-bye.
(Leonard:)What are you looking at?
You've never seen a hypocrite before?